Brother.
Aren't we moving a bit too fast?
Should we wait for the team behind us?
Let's stop for now.
Zhang Tianyou made our Wan Family lead,
to use your Yin-Yang Eyes to spot danger.
He really treats us like his servants.
I trust Brother Tianyou.
He will lead us to the Tidal Tomb.
Let's wait here for the main group.
Take a break.
Chun'er,
don't trust Zhang Tianyou too easily.
I'm the only one you can trust here.
Chun'er?
Brother,
don't these guys seem a bit off to you?
Is there something wrong with this forest,
or...
Zhang Tianyou, is this the right way?
The Wan Family has been ahead for a while.
Only when we reach the general vicinity
can the Dragon-Seeking Ruler pinpoint it.
The Qi Family is struggling in the rear.
Let's wait and take a short break.
What's wrong, Father?
Wan Family leads, Qi Family at the rear.
It's just like twenty years ago, isn't it?
Except twenty years ago,
Not just the Mei Family and Sheng Family.
Rat Bro, go scout ahead.
Slow the Wan Family down.
Got it.
Li Xiao
Stop chasing him.
Let him run.
With his death-seeking nature,
I'm sure he'll follow right behind us.
Family Head, it's Li Xiao.
I saw.
Tianyou said
the treasures left in this tomb
Marshal Li has coveted for over 20 years.
He won't give up easily.
Let's keep moving.
Yes.
I'll go check on Rat.
This...
Family Head.
Let's just wait here.
Brother.
Look, their movements are synchronized.
The miasma here is making them delirious.
Chun'er, the Soul-Startling Whistle!
Father
Maybe I should go take a look too.
Wait here for a moment. Don't move.
Father!
Zhang Tianyou.
What's wrong?
In the past, the Sheng Family and I
did a lot of things to wrong you.
We hurt your pride.
Actually, I...
Where did Rat Bro go?
Actually, about that...
You don't need to say this.
It's not like I hold grudges.
Of course I know you don't hold grudges.
Or you wouldn't have brought us here.
This is a letter of divorce.
From now on,
we have nothing to do with each other.
Also,
I want to remind you,
Mei Yuanhe.
Rat Bro!
What's going on?
Something's wrong.
Gro...
Ground rat!
You...
What... What's wrong with me?
Weren't you just...
Let go!
Father, hurry and save him!
Zhang Tianyou!
It's the miasma in the woods!
Hurry, save him!
Let go!
Zhang Tianyou!
Zhang Tianyou, I'm Jiushuang!
Zhang Tianyou, let go!
Zhang Tianyou!
Wake up!
Tianyou!
Are you okay?
Feeling better?
Here.
Chief, how did even you get affected?
This shouldn't have happened.
What? I'm not dead.
Means we're closer to our destination.
The closer we get, the weirder it gets.
If you're all like this,
the Wan Family siblings must be in danger.
We have to hurry and save them.
Wait.
We're almost there now.
Our priority is to lose our tail.
Family Head Mei.
Take men to find the Wan Family siblings.
You two, come with me.
Jiushuang, don't go with him.
Jiushuang.
Uncle Mei,
worried Zhang Tianyou will harm her?
Don't shoot!
Put your guns down!
Father!
I sneaked back when they weren't looking.
Good.
Father,
you have no idea.
I totally fooled them.
We just need to follow them quietly,
and we'll locate the Tidal Tomb.
Good boy!
I knew you could do it.
For brains, it's gotta be you.
If your Father
had been as smart as you,
twenty years ago,
I wouldn't have made a wasted trip.
By the way,
are those idiots actually capable?
If not,
I'll have men level this place with bombs.
There's no way we won't find that tomb.
Father,
we're here for archaeology,
not to wipe out bandits.
Right, right.
Okay,
we'll do as you say.
What are you standing around for?
Send a few men ahead, left and right,
to scout the area!
What if someone snipes at us?
Yes, Marshal.
Father,
aren't you being too cautious?
Out here, how could there be...
Marshal! Young Master!
There's something...
There's something in the woods ahead!
What?
Xiao Liu Zi...
Xiao Liu Zi was dragged away!
Wait.
What was it? Tell me!
A white shadow...
It was a white blur.
It... it was incredibly strong.
Right down in that hollow.
The hollow?
What... what are you doing?